<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Light Keyboard</string>
    <string name="setup_title">Light Keyboard</string>
    <string name="setup_blurb">A minimal black-and-white keyboard for the Light Phone. Two quick steps:</string>
    <string name="setup_step1">1. Enable Light Keyboard</string>
    <string name="setup_step2">2. Choose it as your keyboard</string>
    <string name="setup_enabled">✓ Enabled</string>
    <string name="setup_done">Setup complete. It will appear in every text field. Swipe down on the keyboard to close it.</string>
    <string name="setup_autocorrect">Autocorrect</string>
    <string name="setup_autocorrect_sub">Fix misspellings as you type, using built-in English and Hebrew dictionaries that also learn the words you use. Works fully offline.</string>
    <string name="setup_languages">Languages</string>
    <string name="setup_languages_sub">English and Hebrew. The globe key switches between them; the emoji key opens emoji. Each language has its own dictionary, autocorrect, and voice input. Long-press a letter for its number/symbol or accents (English) / vowel points (Hebrew); long-press the period to dictate; double-tap space for “. ”; slide on the space bar to move the cursor.</string>
    <string name="setup_number_row">Number row</string>
    <string name="setup_number_row_sub">Show a row of numbers above the letters.</string>
    <string name="setup_auto_cap">Auto-capitalize</string>
    <string name="setup_auto_cap_sub">Capitalize the first letter of each sentence (English).</string>
    <string name="setup_double_space">Double-space for period</string>
    <string name="setup_double_space_sub">Tap the space bar twice to insert “. ”.</string>
    <string name="setup_haptic_sub">Vibration strength on each key press. Tap to cycle.</string>
    <string name="setup_tip">Tip: hold the globe key (⚙) on the keyboard for a quick-settings panel — haptics, autocorrect, auto-capitalize, double-space and number row, without leaving the app you\'re in.</string>
    <string name="setup_prediction">Word completion</string>
    <string name="setup_prediction_sub">Suggest the rest of the word as you type (English and Hebrew), shown underlined after the cursor. Press space to complete it; keep typing to ignore.</string>
    <string name="setup_voice">Voice dictation</string>
    <string name="setup_voice_sub">English is private and on-device (downloads 40 MB once). Hebrew uses the phone\'s own voice service, which may need a connection.</string>
    <string name="setup_voice_clear">Delete voice model (frees ~40 MB)</string>

    <!-- IME subtype labels (system language switcher). -->
    <string name="subtype_en">English</string>
    <string name="subtype_he">עברית</string>
</resources>
